Inventory of the Chiang Kai-shek Diaries
Hoover Institution Archives
Chiang Kai-shek diaries
1917-1972
2006C37
Hoover Institution Archives
76 manuscript boxes (31.6 linear feet)
Photocopies of edited (redacted) and unedited diaries relating to political and military events in China.
Chiang, Kai-shek, 1887-1975
Conditions of Use
Before examining the paper copies of the diaries, users must sign an agreement stating that (1) quotations from the diaries may not be published, broadcast, or redistributed in any form, without the written permission of the Chiang family, which retains copyright; (2) the diaries may not be photocopied nor photographed, so only handwritten notes may be taken; (3) cameras, cell phones, computers, scanners, and other image capture devices, as well as tape recorders and other recording devices, are not allowed while using the diaries; and (4) violations of the agreement may result in forfeiture of the privilege to access materials at the Hoover Institution Library and Archives.
Diaries from 1917 to 1931 (boxes 1-8), 1932 to 1945 (boxes 36-44), 1946-1955 (boxes 45-51) and 1956-1972 (boxes 65-76) are open for research.
Acquisition Information
The original personal diaries of Chiang Kai-shek were deposited at the Hoover Institution in December 2004 by Elizabeth Chiang Fang Chih-yi. The originals are dated from 1917 to 1923 and 1925 to 1972. The diaries will remain in the Archives for fifty years or until a permanent repository is found on the territory of China.
Custodial History
After Chiang's death on April 5, 1975, his personal diaries were given directly to his son, Chiang Ching-kuo. They were later obtained by Chiang Ching-kuo's youngest son, Eddie Chiang Hsiao-yung, the late husband of the depositor, Elizabeth Chiang Fang Chih-yi.
Biographical Note
Chinese political and military leader; head of state, 1928-1949; president of Taiwan, 1949-1975.
Scope and Content of Collection
The original personal diaries of Chiang Kai-shek were deposited at the Hoover Institution in December 2004 by Elizabeth Chiang Fang Chih-yi. The originals are dated from 1917 to 1923 and 1925 to 1972. The diaries will remain in the Archives for fifty years or until a permanent repository is found on the territory of China.
The Hoover Institution did not receive a diary for 1924. For some years, more than one volume per year overlap in time. One theory that would explain this is that Chiang maintained the volumes in separate cities between which he frequently traveled.
Diaries from 1917 to 1931 were opened on March 31, 2006. In the period covered by these diaries, Chiang Kai-shek rose to the leadership of the Kuomintang (Nationalist Party). After training in the Japanese army from 1909 to 1911, Chiang participated in the revolutionary struggles that established the Chinese Republic and began his association with Sun Yat-sen in the Kuomintang. Chiang founded the Whampoa Military Academy, where the Kuomintang army was trained, in 1924. After Sun's death in 1925, Chiang rose to power by leading the Kuomintang army to defeat the northern warlords and unify China. Chiang split with the leftists of his party in 1927 and spent the rest of his life struggling against the Communists.
Diaries from 1932 to 1945 were opened on April 2, 2007. A few months after the newly open diaries begin in January 1932, Chiang became chief of the General Staff and chairman of the National Military Council. At that time, China was a battleground for warlords, Nationalists, Communists, and Japanese invaders. Chiang focused on eliminating the Chinese Communists, who retreated on the Long March into the remote northwest. On December 12, 1936, Chiang was kidnapped at Xi'an by a Manchurian warlord, the young marshal Zhang Xueliang. After agreeing to work with the Communists to fight the Japanese, Chiang was released. Of course, the diaries also cover the period of the Second Sino-Japanese War, from 1937 to 1945, and Chiang's relationship with such allies as U.S. Army generals Claire Chennault and Joseph Stilwell. This segment of diaries ends in 1945, when U.S. ambassador Patrick Hurley, followed by General George C. Marshall, tried unsuccessfully to bridge differences between Chiang's government and the Communists.
Diaries from 1946 to 1955 were opened on July 18, 2008. In 1946, control of China teetered between Nationalists and Communists as civil war resumed. Chiang led the Nationalist government and its army, which gradually lost territory in the north to the Communists led by Mao Zedong. As civil war worsened and the U.S. suspended aid to Chiang, the Nationalist government battled severe inflation that threatened financial chaos. Chiang declared a series of financial and economic emergency measures in August 1948 that were ultimately unsuccessful. Five months later, in January 1949, Chiang resigned as president of the Republic of China while continuing as leader of the Nationalist party. With a strong military push by the Chinese People's Liberation Army beginning in the spring, the Nationalist forces retreated in December 1949 to Taiwan, where Chiang established a stronghold for his party. He resumed his position as president in March 1950, and was reelected by the National Assembly in 1954. Having lamented in his diary about the disintegration and rot from within that led to his party's failure, Chiang established the Central Reform Committee in 1950 to revitalize the party and its principles, reestablish the state in a new milieu, advance his vision for China and Taiwan, and begin laying the groundwork for Taiwan's eventual economic success.
On July 8, 2009, the diaries from 1956 to 1972 were opened. This period draws attention to Taiwan's transformation from a postwar island frontier to the epicenter of the Nationalist China regime. As inflation dropped steadily and the economy grew, Chiang was reelected president by the National Assembly in 1960, 1966, and 1972. The KMT, with Chiang taking the reins as the zongcai (director-general), instituted comprehensive industrial, agricultural, economic, and social reforms. Chiang made land available to farmers at affordable prices and provided state support to industries to nurture their competitiveness internationally. The construction of Taiwans highway system was also completed.
With these reforms came repression as Taiwan functioned as an authoritarian state. The White Terror era ensued, in which the formation of opposition political parties was denounced and pro-democratic/pro-independence figures, like Lei Zhen, were arrested and jailed.
Tension in the Taiwan Strait intensified when Mao continued to launch attacks against Chiang’s troops in the Quemoy and Ma–tsu Islands in 1958. As commander in chief of the military, Chiang held steadfast to his unrelenting objective of counterattacking the Chinese Communists and recovering Mainland China. Though the U.S. Congress passed the Formosa Resolution (January 1955) --a joint security that a joint security pact that authorized President Eisenhower to use U.S. forces to defend the ROC against armed attack--Chiang was unable to garner more American support, and he devised several failed military campaigns.
At the forefront of Chiangs political discussions and thoughts was the U.S. military presence in Cuba and Southeast Asia, particularly Vietnam. Taiwan served as a military and supply base for the U.S. during the height of the Vietnam War.
July 22, 1972, marks Chiangs last noted diary entry. Months earlier, President Nixon had visited China. The announcement of that visit triggered a United Nations vote to give the People's Republic of China a seat in the U.N., effectively expelling Taiwan. Anti-U.S. riots followed on the island.
When Chiang died in 1975, Taiwan remained a one-party state controlled by the Kuomintang. Chiang's son, Chiang Ching-kuo, assumed party leadership and within a few years also became president.
Redactions
The original diaries contain sentences that were crossed out in ink. It is believed that these redactions were made years ago by Chiang Kai-shek, Chiang Ching-kuo, or another individual.
Since the diaries were deposited at Hoover, the Chiang family has been reviewing their contents and is choosing to keep some passages private until 2035. These will be redacted from the use copies with a "2006," "2007," or "2008" annotation in the margin to distinguish them from the earlier redactions.
Related Material
Transcriptions of Chiang's diaries are located in the Second Historical Archives in Nanjing, China, under the collection title Jiang Jieshi Riji Leichao. Photocopies of the transcriptions are located in the Academic Historica in Taipei, Taiwan, and the Kuomintang Party Archives in Taipei, Taiwan.
Accounts of Chiang's early years, including diary excerpts, have been published in several books, such as Mao Sicheng's Minguo Shi Wu Nian Yi Qian Zhi Jiang Jieshi Xian Sheng and Qin Xiaoyi's Zongtong Jianggong Dashi Chang bian. Diary excerpts were also published by the Academia Historica in a continuing series, Shilue Gaoben (1927-1949), attributed to Chiang's colleagues, Sun Yi, Wang Yugao and Wang Yuzheng. These texts were written in the Spring and Autumn Annals (Chun Qiu) style of historiography by blending passages from Chiang's diaries, letters, official papers, etc., to chronologically outline significant events in his personal, military and political life.
China--History--Republic, 1912-1949.; Statesmen--China.
- Diaries [Use Copies], 1917-1972
  - 1917 (Box-folder 1: 1)
  - 1918
    - January 1918 (Box-folder 1: 2)
    - February 1918 (Box-folder 1: 3)
    - March 1918 (Box-folder 1: 4)
    - April 1918 (Box-folder 1: 5)
    - May 1918 (Box-folder 1: 6)
    - June 1918 (Box-folder 1: 7)
    - July 1918 (Box-folder 1: 8)
    - August 1918 (Box-folder 1: 9)
    - September 1918 (Box-folder 1: 10)
    - October 1918 (Box-folder 1: 11)
    - November 1918 (Box-folder 1: 12)
    - December 1918 (Box-folder 1: 13)
  - 1919
    - General 1919 (Box-folder 1: 14)
    - March 1919 (Box-folder 1: 15)
    - April 1919 (Box-folder 1: 16)
    - May 1919 (Box-folder 1: 17)
    - June 1919 (Box-folder 1: 18)
    - July 1919 (Box-folder 1: 19)
    - August 1919 (Box-folder 1: 20)
    - September 1919 (Box-folder 1: 21)
    - October 1919 (Box-folder 2: 1)
    - November 1919 (Box-folder 2: 2)
    - December 1919 (Box-folder 2: 3)
  - 1920
    - January 1920 (Box-folder 2: 4)
    - February 1920 (Box-folder 2: 5)
    - March 1920 (Box-folder 2: 6)
    - April 1920 (Box-folder 2: 7)
    - May 1920 (Box-folder 2: 8)
    - June 1920 (Box-folder 2: 9)
    - July 1920 (Box-folder 2: 10)
    - August 1920 (Box-folder 2: 11)
    - September 1920 (Box-folder 2: 12)
    - October 1920 (Box-folder 2: 13)
    - November 1920 (Box-folder 2: 14)
    - December 1920 (Box-folder 2: 15)
  - 1921
    - January 1921 (Box-folder 2: 16)
    - February 1921 (Box-folder 2: 17)
    - March 1921 (Box-folder 2: 18)
    - April 1921 (Box-folder 2: 19)
    - May 1921 (Box-folder 2: 20)
    - June 1921 (Box-folder 2: 21)
    - July 1921 (Box-folder 2: 22)
    - August 1921 (Box-folder 2: 23)
    - September 1921 (Box-folder 3: 1)
    - October 1921 (Box-folder 3: 2)
    - November 1921 (Box-folder 3: 3)
    - December 1921 (Box-folder 3: 4)
  - 1922
    - January 1922 (Box-folder 3: 5)
    - February 1922 (Box-folder 3: 6)
    - March 1922 (Box-folder 3: 7)
    - April 1922 (Box-folder 3: 8)
    - May 1922 (Box-folder 3: 9)
    - June 1922 (Box-folder 3: 10)
    - July 1922 (Box-folder 3: 11)
    - August 1922 (Box-folder 3: 12)
    - September 1922 (Box-folder 3: 13)
    - October 1922 (Box-folder 3: 14)
    - November 1922 (Box-folder 3: 15)
    - December 1922 (Box-folder 3: 16)
  - 1923
    - January 1923 (Box-folder 3: 17)
    - February 1923 (Box-folder 3: 18)
    - March 1923 (Box-folder 3: 19)
    - April 1923 (Box-folder 3: 20)
    - May 1923 (Box-folder 3: 21)
    - June 1923 (Box-folder 3: 22)
    - July 1923 (Box-folder 3: 23)
    - August 1923 (Box-folder 4: 1)
    - September 1923 (Box-folder 4: 2)
    - October 1923 (Box-folder 4: 3)
    - November 1923 (Box-folder 4: 4)
    - December 1923 (Box-folder 4: 5)
  - 1925
    - January 1925 (Box-folder 4: 6)
    - February 1925 (Box-folder 4: 7)
    - March 1925 (Box-folder 4: 8)
    - April 1925 (Box-folder 4: 9)
    - May 1925 (Box-folder 4: 10)
    - June 1925 (Box-folder 4: 11)
    - July 1925 (Box-folder 4: 12)
    - August 1925 (Box-folder 4: 13)
    - September 1925 (Box-folder 4: 14)
    - October 1925 (Box-folder 4: 15)
    - November 1925 (Box-folder 4: 16)
    - December 1925 (Box-folder 4: 17)
  - 1926
    - January 1926 (Box-folder 4: 18)
    - February 1926 (Box-folder 4: 19)
    - March 1926 (Box-folder 4: 20)
    - April 1926 (Box-folder 4: 21)
    - May 1926 (Box-folder 4: 22)
    - June 1926 (Box-folder 4: 23)
    - July 1926 (Box-folder 5: 1)
    - August 1926 (Box-folder 5: 2)
    - September 1926 (Box-folder 5: 3)
    - October 1926 (Box-folder 5: 4)
    - November 1926 (Box-folder 5: 5)
    - December 1926 (Box-folder 5: 6)
  - 1927
    - January 1927 (Box-folder 5: 7)
    - February 1927 (Box-folder 5: 8)
    - March 1927 (Box-folder 5: 9)
    - April 1927 (Box-folder 5: 10)
    - May 1927 (Box-folder 5: 11)
    - June 1927 (Box-folder 5: 12)
    - July 1927 (Box-folder 5: 13)
    - August 1927 (Box-folder 5: 14)
    - September 1927 (Box-folder 5: 15)
    - October 1927 (Box-folder 5: 16)
    - November 1927 (Box-folder 5: 17)
    - December 1927 (Box-folder 5: 18)
  - 1928
    - Volume One
      - January 1928 (Box-folder 5: 19)
      - February 1928 (Box-folder 5: 20)
      - March-December 1928 (Box-folder 6: 1)
    - Volume Two
      - March 1928 (Box-folder 6: 2)
      - April 1928 (Box-folder 6: 3)
      - May 1928 (Box-folder 6: 4)
      - June 1928 (Box-folder 6: 5)
      - July 1928 (Box-folder 6: 6)
      - August 1928 (Box-folder 6: 7)
      - September 1928 (Box-folder 6: 8)
      - October 1928 (Box-folder 6: 9)
      - November 1928 (Box-folder 6: 10)
      - December 1928 (Box-folder 6: 11)
  - 1929
    - Volume One
      - January 1929 (Box-folder 6: 12)
      - February 1929 (Box-folder 6: 13)
      - March 1929 (Box-folder 6: 14)
      - April 1929 (Box-folder 6: 15)
      - May 1929 (Box-folder 6: 16)
      - June 1929 (Box-folder 6: 17)
      - July 1929 (Box-folder 6: 18)
      - August 1929 (Box-folder 7: 1)
    - Volume Two
      - January-August 1929 (Box-folder 7: 2)
      - September 1929 (Box-folder 7: 3)
      - October 1929 (Box-folder 7: 4)
      - November 1929 (Box-folder 7: 5)
      - December 1929 (Box-folder 7: 6)
  - 1930
    - January 1930 (Box-folder 7: 7)
    - February 1930 (Box-folder 7: 8)
    - March 1930 (Box-folder 7: 9)
    - April 1930 (Box-folder 7: 10)
    - May 1930 (Box-folder 7: 11)
    - June 1930 (Box-folder 7: 12)
    - July 1930 (Box-folder 7: 13)
    - August 1930 (Box-folder 7: 14)
    - September 1930 (Box-folder 7: 15)
    - October 1930 (Box-folder 7: 16)
    - November 1930 (Box-folder 7: 17)
    - December 1930 (Box-folder 8: 1)
  - 1931
    - January 1931 (Box-folder 8: 2)
    - February 1931 (Box-folder 8: 3)
    - March 1931 (Box-folder 8: 4)
    - April 1931 (Box-folder 8: 5)
    - May 1931 (Box-folder 8: 6)
    - June 1931 (Box-folder 8: 7)
    - July 1931 (Box-folder 8: 8)
    - August 1931 (Box-folder 8: 9)
    - September 1931 (Box-folder 8: 10)
    - October 1931 (Box-folder 8: 11)
    - November 1931 (Box-folder 8: 12)
    - December 1931 (Box-folder 8: 13)
  - CLOSED (Box 9-35)
  - 1932
    - January 1932 (Box-folder 36: 1)
    - February 1932 (Box-folder 36: 2)
    - March 1932 (Box-folder 36: 3)
    - April 1932 (Box-folder 36: 4)
    - May 1932 (Box-folder 36: 5)
    - June 1932 (Box-folder 36: 6)
    - July 1932 (Box-folder 36: 7)
    - August 1932 (Box-folder 36: 8)
    - September 1932 (Box-folder 36: 9)
    - October 1932 (Box-folder 36: 10)
    - November 1932 (Box-folder 36: 11)
    - December 1932 (Box-folder 36: 12)
  - 1933
    - January 1933 (Box-folder 36: 13)
    - February 1933 (Box-folder 36: 14)
    - March 1933 (Box-folder 36: 15)
    - April 1933 (Box-folder 36: 16)
    - May 1933 (Box-folder 36: 17)
    - June 1933 (Box-folder 36: 18)
    - July 1933 (Box-folder 36: 19)
    - August 1933 (Box-folder 36: 20)
    - September 1933 (Box-folder 36: 21)
    - October 1933 (Box-folder 36: 22)
    - November 1933 (Box-folder 37: 1)
    - December 1933 (Box-folder 37: 2)
  - 1934
    - January 1934 (Box-folder 37: 3)
    - February 1934 (Box-folder 37: 4)
    - March 1934 (Box-folder 37: 5)
    - April 1934 (Box-folder 37: 6)
    - May 1934 (Box-folder 37: 7)
    - June 1934 (Box-folder 37: 8)
    - July 1934 (Box-folder 37: 9)
    - August 1934 (Box-folder 37: 10)
    - September 1934 (Box-folder 37: 11)
    - October 1934 (Box-folder 37: 12)
    - November 1934 (Box-folder 37: 13)
    - December 1934 (Box-folder 37: 14)
  - 1935
    - January 1935 (Box-folder 37: 15)
    - February 1935 (Box-folder 37: 16)
    - March 1935 (Box-folder 37: 17)
    - April 1935 (Box-folder 37: 18)
    - May 1935 (Box-folder 38: 1)
    - June 1935 (Box-folder 38: 2)
    - July 1935 (Box-folder 38: 3)
    - August 1935 (Box-folder 38: 4)
    - September 1935 (Box-folder 38: 5)
    - October 1935 (Box-folder 38: 6)
    - November 1935 (Box-folder 38: 7)
    - December 1935 (Box-folder 38: 8)
  - 1936
    - January 1936 (Box-folder 38: 9)
    - February 1936 (Box-folder 38: 10)
    - March 1936 (Box-folder 38: 11)
    - April 1936 (Box-folder 38: 12)
    - May 1936 (Box-folder 38: 13)
    - June 1936 (Box-folder 38: 14)
    - July 1936 (Box-folder 38: 15)
    - August 1936 (Box-folder 39: 1)
    - September 1936 (Box-folder 39: 2)
    - October 1936 (Box-folder 39: 3)
    - November 1936 (Box-folder 39: 4)
    - December 1936 (Box-folder 39: 5)
  - 1937
    - General 1937 (Box-folder 39: 6)
    - January 1937 (Box-folder 39: 7)
    - February 1937 (Box-folder 39: 8)
    - March 1937 (Box-folder 39: 9)
    - April 1937 (Box-folder 39: 10)
    - May 1937 (Box-folder 39: 11)
    - June 1937 (Box-folder 39: 12)
    - July 1937 (Box-folder 39: 13)
    - August 1937 (Box-folder 39: 14)
    - September 1937 (Box-folder 39: 15)
    - October 1937 (Box-folder 39: 16)
    - November 1937 (Box-folder 39: 17)
    - December 1937 (Box-folder 39: 18)
  - 1938
    - General 1938 (Box-folder 39: 19)
    - January 1938 (Box-folder 39: 20)
    - February 1938 (Box-folder 39: 21)
    - March 1938 (Box-folder 39: 22)
    - April 1938 (Box-folder 39: 23)
    - May 1938 (Box-folder 39: 24)
    - June 1938 (Box-folder 39: 25)
    - July 1938 (Box-folder 39: 26)
    - August 1938 (Box-folder 39: 27)
    - September 1938 (Box-folder 39: 28)
    - October 1938 (Box-folder 39: 29)
    - November 1938 (Box-folder 40: 1)
    - December 1938 (Box-folder 40: 2)
  - 1939
    - General 1939 (Box-folder 40: 3)
    - January 1939 (Box-folder 40: 4)
    - February 1939 (Box-folder 40: 5)
    - March 1939 (Box-folder 40: 6)
    - April 1939 (Box-folder 40: 7)
    - May 1939 (Box-folder 40: 8)
    - June 1939 (Box-folder 40: 9)
    - July 1939 (Box-folder 40: 10)
    - August 1939 (Box-folder 40: 11)
    - September 1939 (Box-folder 40: 12)
    - October 1939 (Box-folder 40: 13)
    - November 1939 (Box-folder 40: 14)
    - December 1939 (Box-folder 40: 15)
  - 1940
    - Volume One 1940
      - General 1940 (Box-folder 40: 16)
      - January 1940 (Box-folder 40: 17)
      - February 1940 (Box-folder 40: 18)
      - March 1940 (Box-folder 40: 19)
      - April 1940 (Box-folder 40: 20)
      - May 1940 (Box-folder 40: 21)
      - June 1940 (Box-folder 40: 22)
      - July 1940 (Box-folder 40: 23)
      - August 1940 (Box-folder 40: 24)
      - September 1940 (Box-folder 40: 25)
      - October 1940 (Box-folder 40: 26)
      - November 1940 (Box-folder 40: 27)
      - December 1940 (Box-folder 40: 28)
    - Volume Two 1940
      - General, General (January) 1940 (Box-folder 41: 1)
      - February 1940 (Box-folder 41: 2)
      - Part Two 1940 (Box-folder 41: 3)
      - Part Three 1940 (Box-folder 41: 4)
      - Part Four 1940 (Box-folder 41: 5)
  - 1941
    - Volume One 1941
      - General 1941 (Box-folder 41: 6)
      - January 1941 (Box-folder 41: 7)
      - February 1941 (Box-folder 41: 8)
      - March 1941 (Box-folder 41: 9)
      - April 1941 (Box-folder 41: 10)
      - May 1941 (Box-folder 41: 11)
      - June 1941 (Box-folder 41: 12)
      - July 1941 (Box-folder 41: 13)
      - August 1941 (Box-folder 41: 14)
      - September 1941 (Box-folder 41: 15)
      - October 1941 (Box-folder 41: 16)
      - November 1941 (Box-folder 41: 17)
      - December 1941 (Box-folder 41: 18)
    - Volume Two 1941
      - General 1941 (Box-folder 42: 1)
      - October 1941 (Box-folder 42: 2)
      - November 1941 (Box-folder 42: 3)
      - December 1941 (Box-folder 42: 4)
  - 1942
    - Volume One 1942
      - General 1942 (Box-folder 42: 5)
      - January 1942 (Box-folder 42: 6)
      - February 1942 (Box-folder 42: 7)
      - March 1942 (Box-folder 42: 8)
      - April 1942 (Box-folder 42: 9)
      - May 1942 (Box-folder 42: 10)
      - June 1942 (Box-folder 42: 11)
      - July 1942 (Box-folder 42: 12)
      - August 1942 (Box-folder 42: 13)
      - September 1942 (Box-folder 42: 14)
      - October 1942 (Box-folder 42: 15)
      - November 1942 (Box-folder 42: 16)
      - December 1942 (Box-folder 42: 17)
    - Volume Two 1942
      - General, General (January) 1942 (Box-folder 42: 18)
      - February 1942 (Box-folder 42: 19)
      - March 1942 (Box-folder 42: 20)
      - April 1942 (Box-folder 42: 21)
  - 1943
    - General 1943 (Box-folder 42: 22)
    - January 1943 (Box-folder 42: 23)
    - February 1943 (Box-folder 43: 1)
    - March 1943 (Box-folder 43: 2)
    - April 1943 (Box-folder 43: 3)
    - May 1943 (Box-folder 43: 4)
    - June 1943 (Box-folder 43: 5)
    - July 1943 (Box-folder 43: 6)
    - August 1943 (Box-folder 43: 7)
    - September 1943 (Box-folder 43: 8)
    - October 1943 (Box-folder 43: 9)
    - November 1943 (Box-folder 43: 10)
    - December 1943 (Box-folder 43: 11)
  - 1944
    - General 1944 (Box-folder 43: 12)
    - January 1944 (Box-folder 43: 13)
    - February 1944 (Box-folder 43: 14)
    - March 1944 (Box-folder 43: 15)
    - April 1944 (Box-folder 43: 16)
    - May 1944 (Box-folder 43: 17)
    - June 1944 (Box-folder 43: 18)
    - July 1944 (Box-folder 43: 19)
    - August 1944 (Box-folder 43: 20)
    - September 1944 (Box-folder 43: 21)
    - October 1944 (Box-folder 43: 22)
    - November 1944 (Box-folder 43: 23)
    - December 1944 (Box-folder 43: 24)
  - 1945
    - General 1945 (Box-folder 44: 1)
    - January 1945 (Box-folder 44: 2)
    - February 1945 (Box-folder 44: 3)
    - March 1945 (Box-folder 44: 4)
    - April 1945 (Box-folder 44: 5)
    - May 1945 (Box-folder 44: 6)
    - June 1945 (Box-folder 44: 7)
    - July 1945 (Box-folder 44: 8)
    - August 1945 (Box-folder 44: 9)
    - September 1945 (Box-folder 44: 10)
    - October 1945 (Box-folder 44: 11)
    - November 1945 (Box-folder 44: 12)
    - December 1945 (Box-folder 44: 13)
  - 1946
    - Volume One 1946
      - General 1946 (Box-folder 45: 1)
      - January 1946 (Box-folder 45: 2)
      - February 1946 (Box-folder 45: 3)
      - March 1946 (Box-folder 45: 4)
      - April 1946 (Box-folder 45: 5)
      - May 1946 (Box-folder 45: 6)
      - June 1946 (Box-folder 45: 7)
      - July 1946 (Box-folder 45: 8)
      - August 1946 (Box-folder 45: 9)
      - September 1946 (Box-folder 45: 10)
      - October 1946 (Box-folder 45: 11)
      - November 1946 (Box-folder 45: 12)
      - December 1946 (Box-folder 45: 13)
    - Volume Two 1946
      - Part Three 1946 (Box-folder 46: 1)
      - Part Four 1946 (Box-folder 46: 2)
  - 1947
    - General 1947 (Box-folder 46: 3)
    - January 1947 (Box-folder 46: 4)
    - February 1947 (Box-folder 46: 5)
    - March 1947 (Box-folder 46: 6)